<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Jeff Lee</title>
		<link>http://jefflee.xyz/</link>
		<description>The personal blog of Jeff Lee</description>
		<copyright>2017</copyright>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 01:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 01:04:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<item>
			<title>24 Hours on the Test Track</title>
			<link>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/2017-subaru-casa-cycling-challenge-24-hours-on-the-test-track</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="http://casasforkidsfund.kintera.org/faf/home/default.asp?ievent=1170055"&gt;Subaru CASA Cycling Challenge&lt;/a&gt; takes place each year at the Subaru of Indiana Automotive two mile oval test track in Lafayette. It allows individuals and teams to test their endurance over a 24-hour period while raising funds to support the CASAs for Kids Fund. There are three categories: Solo men, solo women, and team. For the teams the ride is like a relay, with only one member of a team on the track at a time. In 2017 there were 42 teams (each with several riders), 25 solo men, and 9 solo women.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<enclosure url="http://jefflee.xyz/images/end-of-race.JPG" length="0" type="image" />
			<guid>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/2017-subaru-casa-cycling-challenge-24-hours-on-the-test-track</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href='http://casasforkidsfund.kintera.org/faf/home/default.asp?ievent=1170055'&gt;Subaru CASA Cycling Challenge&lt;/a&gt; takes place each year at the Subaru of Indiana Automotive two mile oval test track in Lafayette. It allows individuals and teams to test their endurance over a 24-hour period while raising funds to support the CASAs for Kids Fund. There are three categories: Solo men, solo women, and team. For the teams the ride is like a relay, with only one member of a team on the track at a time. In 2017 there were 42 teams (each with several riders), 25 solo men, and 9 solo women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joy and I got to the Subaru plant and set up our tent in the infield. She would sleep there tonight, while my plan was to ride for the entire 24 hours and not sleep at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were lots of riders on the track at the start of the race at 10:00 in the morning. I stayed near the back of the pack. Most of the time I ride by myself, and I was little nervous riding with so many people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0242.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;At the start.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
 
The headwind was stiff as I came around the first curve, and I immediately regretted not attaching my old, rarely used pair of clip-on aero bars to the handlebars. About 75% of the participants were riding either dedicated triathlon bikes or road bikes fitted with aero bars. I didn't see any other single-speeds. (In fact, I never saw anyone riding a single-speed during the entire event, something which surprised me; I expected to see at least a few track bikes, given that this event was on a track. Wrong kind of track, I guess.)
&lt;p&gt;In the first few laps I recognized Molly Birt, last year's solo female winner, rode up beside her, and jokingly asked if I could purchase her aero bars. She seemed unamused, and I felt kind of dumb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few laps later, though, Stephen Strayer, last year's solo male winner (he did better by himself than all but two relay teams!) briefly slowed down and said hello. That was nice of him. He asked what my longest ride ever was, I told him 160 miles, and he assured that I'd shatter that record today. He also said that the night-time would determine the winner of the race. Stephen was prescient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After ten laps (20 miles) I stopped briefly, rode into the infield, and looked at the electronic scoreboard with Joy. &amp;quot;You're in the middle of the pack,&amp;quot; she informed me. I'd been riding as fast as I could, and was a little disappointed to be that far back in the solo male category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that, Joy left and went to visit her friend April, who lived in town, and I got back on the bike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Temperatures were mild, but it was sunny, and I sweated as I maintained a decent pace, averaging over 19 mph for the first 50 laps. I took a handful of  quick breaks to drink and eat snacks, and then at 100 miles I stopped and went back to our tent site. I cleaned all the salt off my face, reapplied sunblock, and chugged two bottles of coconut water from our cooler. I love coconut water, but that might have been a mistake, and I briefly thought I was going to throw up. I'd brought two other sets of bike clothes, but I decided not to change, since what I was wearing was working well so far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd stopped longer than I planned. I checked the standings to find that my position had improved a little, then got back on the bike a little at 4:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My average speed started dropping during the second hundred miles. I attempted drafting a few times, but couldn't hold on to the lines of the fast relay team riders. I started making more frequent stops at the event's support tent, eating many cookies and an occasional banana. Joy came back before dusk, and we talked a while. My original &amp;quot;race plan&amp;quot; was to get off the bike for no more than one hour of the 24 hour event. Obviously that wasn't happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0262-c.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As it grew dark, I put the lights on the bike, and changed from my sunglasses to clear lenses. This would be the first time I'd done any extended riding in the dark. Bugs came out for a few laps, and coated my arms. Ugh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a few lights around the track, but they weren't very bright, so everyone was required to have headlights and tail lights on their bikes. Even so, I started hugging the inside of the track, because I didn't want to be out in the middle and get hit from behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our tent was in the infield close to the far-side of the track, and Joy cheered me on from there until she went to bed about 11:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some time in the late evening I reached 200 miles. After 100 laps, I was intimately familiar with every bump and crack on the two miles of oval track. I now recognized almost all of the solo riders. One of them was a young guy in his 20's named Tom Bruecker, and I would occasionally ride alongside and chat with him. He'd previously done this race as part of a relay team, so it was interesting to hear his perspectives on those very different experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wind finally died down very early in the morning, it was cool (although not so cool that I needed a jacket), and the bugs weren't too bothersome. One of the event volunteers, an indefatigable older lady, cheered me on virtually every time time I made it around the track. By now she knew the names of the all the solo riders who hadn't give up yet, and she called out our names as we passed where she was standing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was startled once when I encountered an ambulance on the dark track. One of the fast relay riders had crashed while drafting another rider. I don't like riding an inch or two behind another rider's wheel even in broad daylight, and I can't imagine trying it at night with only a weak headlight. I heard later that he broke his collarbone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom Bruecker started riding faster, and I couldn't keep up - I felt that if I pushed myself any harder I'd throw up. He moved into second place behind the leader, Stephen Strayer, who, according to the scoreboard, hadn't ridden in a couple of hours. (After the race Stephen told me that once he realized he couldn't beat his own course record, he decided to sleep for a few hours.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 230 miles, around 3:30 in the morning, I found it difficult to continue. I started taking increasingly frequent, longer breaks at the support tent, eating bananas, sipping Diet Coke, watching the standings on the scoreboard, and trying not to vomit. I was now in fourth place, behind Stephen Strayer the leader, then Tom B., then someone named Tom Mueller. WHO WAS HE? I asked every man who came into the support tent, but none of them was the elusive Tom Mueller.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I began bargaining with myself - &amp;quot;Just 10 more laps, and then you can stop at the tent again.&amp;quot; My butt was hurting, and I was afraid to see what it looked like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the bike, I was, perhaps unreasonably, very annoyed with the fresh relay team riders who kept zooming past me. I was especially irritated with the guy who called out &amp;quot;WHERE ARE YOUR GEARS!?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About an hour before dawn I stopped for yet another break and talked to Tom B.'s wife, who had woken up. She was cheering him on from the sidelines. But she also said she was going to suggest to him that he stop once he got to 300 miles, which earlier he had told me was his personal goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of times I visited the men's restroom, which was was horrific, with pools of pee everywhere. Fortunately I was so dehydrated that I didn't need to stop there very often, or for very long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When dawn broke I felt a little burst of energy. Joy was up now. Tom B., who had been several laps ahead of me, appeared to have stopped riding at 300 miles... was he asleep? I was still in fourth place, but was gaining on him. I told Joy I was going to make a final push to the end, and go for third place. I was five or six laps behind 2nd place rider Tom Mueller, the closest I'd gotten to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0278-c.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sun was up when I finally met Tom Mueller, riding on the track. I rode with him for seven laps, which went much more quickly, now that the sun was out and I had someone to talk to while riding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back at the tent for a break I looked at the standings, and Tom Bruecker walked up, not in bike clothes. He'd quit the race at 300 miles, and my third place result was secure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0295.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Just over one hour to go.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just before 10:00 in the morning, 24 hours after the start of the race, I made my 155th lap around the two mile oval track. I was very tired of riding my bike now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0322-cropped.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;The end.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a brief awards ceremony, where I accepted my third-place solo male plaque, then we (well, Joy) packed everything up, and we headed to our friend April's house where I tried not to fall asleep while I took a shower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0331.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/2017-Subaru-Casa-Challenge/IMG_0333.JPG" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;The nice volunteer who stayed up all night cheering us on.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything hurt, and after spending 20 of the last 24 hours perched on a small, hard saddle, my butt especially was... not so good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, I had a great time doing this. I'll never be very fast on the bike, but I feel good that I never quit, even in the middle of the night when it was extremely difficult to force myself to make yet another lap around the track.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A First Attempt at Touring on a Single-Speed, Day Five</title>
			<link>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-five</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;The Redbud Ride was the Wet Butt ride. The organizers canceled the 100 mile option, with its infamous, steep hills that I'd been looking forward to trying on the single speed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<guid>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-five</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The Redbud Ride was the Wet Butt ride. The organizers canceled the 100 mile option, with its infamous, steep hills that I'd been looking forward to trying on the single speed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter, who had never before intentionally ridden his bicycle in the rain, gamely agreed to do the shortest option, 24 miles, with me. We actually got out early and rode the first three miles before the rain started, but after that it poured on us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was fortunate to have four days of mostly great weather on my &amp;quot;ride to the ride.&amp;quot; I was happy with the performance of the Wabi single speed, with the exception of the wimpy 23 mm tires. I will be replacing those before I try any more touring on the bike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-five-1.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-five-2.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;The guy holding the umbrella was a volunteer at the event, and was impressed that I was riding a single speed: "I like the purity of it."&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-five-3.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-five-4.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A First Attempt at Touring on a Single-Speed, Day Four</title>
			<link>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-four</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Breakfast at the inn was a couple of bananas and approximately half a bag of Krispy Kreme glazed crullers. Charlie had emerged, shirtless, as I walked into the kitchen, and mentioned that I should have "a cruller or two." After he went back upstairs to his quarters I decided not to interpret "a cruller or two" literally, and quickly ate most of the bag instead.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<enclosure url="http://jefflee.xyz/images/kentucky-fence.jpeg" length="0" type="image" />
			<guid>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-four</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Breakfast at the inn was a couple of bananas and approximately half a bag of Krispy Kreme glazed crullers. Charlie had emerged, shirtless, as I walked into the kitchen, and mentioned that I should have &amp;quot;a cruller or two.&amp;quot; After he went back upstairs to his quarters I decided not to interpret &amp;quot;a cruller or two&amp;quot; literally, and quickly ate most of the bag instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rode out under cloudy skies, crossed I-65, and continued on the TransAmerica Trail. The routing had changed since my circa-2006 maps were printed, and now it bypassed Bardstown entirely. That was fine with me, since I remembered it as one of the busiest of the Kentucky sections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since my map was  now useless for a while, I relied on a combination of the &amp;quot;US Bicycle Route 76&amp;quot; signs and the new TransAmerica Trail smartphone app. The new route was really nice - quiet country roads, the kind I choose when I'm making my own route in Kentucky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-1.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-2.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was looking forward to a country store breakfast when I reached the tiny community of Howardstown, but the Mini Mart, which I remembered from my 2006 coast-to-coast trip, was now closed. Judging by the headline on the yellowed newspaper in the box outside announcing the death of Muhammad Ali, it appeared to have been closed for almost a year. Bummer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I left the TransAmerica Trail there and turned south onto State Route 84, which was curvy and tree-lined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-3.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-4.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-5.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-6.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the time I reached Raywick (population 144) the few raindrops I'd been feeling turned into a steady drizzle. I sat in the town park in a picnic pavilion for a while, then put on my rain jacket, rode through town, and stopped at Blandford's store. As I walked in, a guy getting out of his truck said &amp;quot;'Bout to get wet.&amp;quot; For some reason I'm always tempted to argue with the people who seem to enjoy telling me this - I felt like responding &amp;quot;Oh no I'm not! This is a high quality Marmot jacket that will ensure that I stay dry and comfortable!&amp;quot; Instead I just grunted and walked inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chugged a can of pop while I looked at Google Maps. I really had no idea where I was going today, and was literally making a route as I went along now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back on the road I endured about an hour of cold drizzle before the sun came out as I neared Lebanon (population 6,331.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rode on busy US 68 for about a mile, then made a right turn, past the Walmart into an industrial park zone, and rode past several factories and distribution center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was all I saw of Lebanon. I got on State Route 49 for a while. Very little traffic, and a couple of hills to keep things interesting. The sun was beating down now, so I stopped on the side of the road to reapply my &amp;quot;baby&amp;quot; sunblock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a sign outside Bradfordsville (population 304) announcing that the town was the recipient of the &amp;quot;2006 NADO Award for America's Most Innovative Community.&amp;quot; Sounded intriguing, so I decided to be on the lookout for any signs of innovation while I was in town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-7.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I walked into the Superior Food Market, where the air conditioning was definitely NOT working, and purchased a bunch of snacks and drinks and a ham and turkey sandwich, then walked to the back where the farmers and working men were having lunch. Everybody was smoking. I'm pretty sure that except for Las Vegas casinos, rural Kentucky is the only place in the USA where smoking is still so prevalent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the tables were occupied, but one of the men motioned for me to sit down with him, so I ate lunch while we talked. It was a slightly awkward conversation, since the guy was a low talker, who I had to really strain to understand, and he also inserted much-longer-than-normal pauses into his replies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had no problem understanding his accent, though, and in fact, after hanging around all these country stores the last few days, my own Kentucky accent is now approximately 75% thicker than when I left Illinois a few days ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After lunch I headed back out into the bright sunshine, eavesdropped for a minute on a couple talking outside the grocery (&amp;quot;He's gotta go back to jail again!&amp;quot;), then rode out of Bradsfordville on State Route 49, never having observed any NADO Award-Winning innovation during my admittedly brief time in town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a great long, flat section on 49. I got involved in a slow-moving convoy of tractors led by a flag truck for miles, which was fun, since it was one of the rare times I was the fastest vehicle on the road. Unfortunately, I got the 1970's song &amp;quot;Convoy&amp;quot; stuck in my head for the next hour. How awful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-8.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-four-9.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I turned onto another state highway, 78, which was, again, low-traffic, but hillier. I was slowly riding toward the real hills of eastern Kentucky. As I rode past a ramshackle residence, the guy outside called out &amp;quot;Pedal Haaarrder!&amp;quot; I tried to comply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hustonville (population 347), at the intersection of State Route 78 and US 127, was very busy, presumably with end-of-school-day traffic. Eventually I grew weary of this, and pulled over to examine Google Maps. I didn't have any cell service, and the maps were barely functional, but it appeared that I could take a network of back roads and eventually meet up somewhere with my friend Peter, who had agreed to find me on the road. Peter is game for almost anything, so I didn't feel TOO guilty about my self-indulgent zigzagging around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next few hours were a lot of fun. The roads were curvy, tree-lined, and hilly. I stopped at one of the friendliest little country stores yet, Elmores's Market, where the people let me use the store phone to call Peter so that I could attempt to set up a meeting place. As usual, I spent some time talking to the locals, some of whom had pretty pronounced Eastern KY accents - one guy asked his friend what he'd been up to lately, and he responded &amp;quot;I've been stayin' up in that holler - that way I stay out of trouble!&amp;quot; It was interesting how the terrain and the accents had changed over the course of just a couple of days of bike riding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another hour of great riding (and the longest, steepest hill of this tour) and I reached a bustling gas station/convenience store/restaurant on US 27. The road was super-busy, and I decided to call it a day at 96 miles. I phoned Peter to let him know where I was, then hung out at the place for a while eating macaroni and cheese and hush puppies (because, why not?) and chatting with the women working there. They seemed amused by my presence, although they were too polite to comment on my cycling attire, especially my little cycling cap, which probably looks pretty dumb to anyone who doesn't ride a bike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter arrived in his aging mini van, whose battery was apparently dying and would require a jump start if he turned off the engine, and we loaded my bike and stuff and headed toward the town of London, site of tomorrow's Redbud Ride, which, according to the weather forecast, was going to be a rainy ride indeed.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A First Attempt at Touring on a Single-Speed, Day Three</title>
			<link>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-three</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;I was up early, got my small amount of gear loaded quickly, and was riding out of the church when it was barely light.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<enclosure url="http://jefflee.xyz/images/kentucky-2017.jpeg" length="0" type="image" />
			<guid>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-three</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I was up early, got my small amount of gear loaded quickly, and was riding out of the church when it was barely light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-1.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-2.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;My bedroom in the Cyclist Room at the First Baptist Church in Sebree.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My smug self-congratulation on this early start lasted approximately one mile, when I stopped at a convenience store for a quick breakfast that turned into an hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of that hour I was engaged in conversation with a loquacious local, who spoke of various things: The many injuries he suffered as a sheet metal worker, grisly injuries suffered by his coworkers when he worked for the railroad (&amp;quot;It split him like a wishbone... He survived, but needless to say he will never have children&amp;quot;), his love of motorcycles, that one time he rode a bicycle 16 miles, and, especially, his love of guns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn't have a lot to say as he listed the many guns he owned and described their capabilities. He told me that his thirteen-year-old daughter had a gun of her own, and despite his description of the various rules he imposed on her use of the gun, notably that she wasn't allowed to chamber a round inside the house, I was slightly appalled.  It's a good thing that I was not entrusted with a gun when I was thirteen years old - I might have used it to murder my middle school tormentors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first several miles leaving Sebree had a little more traffic than I prefer, but the drivers were well behaved. As I turned off the busy road onto a much quieter one, a pickup truck slowed down, and the driver asked &amp;quot;Do you want a ride? That doesn't look like much fun!&amp;quot; I just laughed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-3.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stopped in tiny Beech Grove, where the only sunblock in the little country store was &amp;quot;baby&amp;quot; sunblock. The old men who always sit at tables at these kinds of places in the mornings chortled at my purchase, but I figured if the sunblock was effective on babies then it should work on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-4.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;The only sunblock available in Beech Grove, Kentucky (population 243). Now I smell like a baby. A big, hairy, sweaty, greasy baby.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-5.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ride continued to be pleasant. By mid morning I'd reached Utica, yesterday's original destination, where I stopped at J.R.'s, another classic Kentucky country store. The old woman who owned the place told me that when she bought the store years ago, she moved the table where the old men sat to the back of the store, so that women would feel comfortable coming in to shop. &amp;quot;Honey, this was a MAN'S place back then!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We talked about the economics of running a country store and competing against the local Dollar General store, and then she walked across the road to her trailer home. Before going inside she looked at me over her shoulder and said &amp;quot;They're a hollerin' for rain!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-6.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not long after that, I stopped at Doolin's, yet ANOTHER country store. I bought a can of pop and talked to the elderly proprietress, who, oddly enough on such a hot day, was dressed in a flannel Christmas-themed outfit. Outside the store, two men walked up and started a conversation with me. One of the men was heavily tattooed, and had the look of someone who knows a lot about automobile engines. He was immediately interested in the single speed bike, and we talked about how well the 48x19 gear performed on the hills. His friend was older and neatly dressed in smoothly ironed khakis. He was one of the guys I always meet on bike tours who are interested in one thing and one thing only about what I'm doing: The tires. &amp;quot;How do those tires hold up?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;How many flats have you had?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Is it hard to fix a flat?&amp;quot; etc. etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-7.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Midday I reached Fordsville (population 524), a busier town with a grimy gas station instead of a country store. There was a young woman chain smoking outside the store, telling all the passersby about her recent legal problems. Not a pleasant scene, so I rode for a mile until, not liking the busy traffic, I pulled over, consulted Google Maps, and quickly figured out a hillier but much less busy route on smaller roads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-8.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-9.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My alternate route dropped me back on to the TransAmerica Trail near Falls of Rough after about an hour of hill climbing and descending. I stopped at the store there, where the friendly woman shouted &amp;quot;My first bicyclist of the year!&amp;quot; She was still excited to see me even after I informed her that I was only doing a week or so on the route, and wasn't crossing the country. After eating a sandwich I had a conversation with an odd guy who advised me to use WD-40 on my chain, and also cautioned me that my tires were dangerously bald (they weren't.) Despite living on the most famous bicycle route in America, he seemed surprised to learn that all the cyclists he'd been seeing for years were (mostly) on long rides from coast-to-coast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was the end of my interactions with people for the next several hours. I stayed on the TransAmerica Trail, which was nice and low-traffic, all the way to Sonora (population 350).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-three-10.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sonora is on Interstate 65. There was supposed to be some sort of bed and breakfast in town, although it had virtually no internet presence, and no one had answered the phone number when I'd called three or four times throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got to Sonora as dusk approached and started looking for the bed and breakfast. I couldn't find it. The address I had did not appear to exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rode to the edge of town, sat on a rock fence in front of the Dollar General store, and considered my options. There appeared to be a motel four or five miles away in another town, but it had truly terrible reviews. It would be dark soon, and I thought I should call the place to make sure it was still in business before riding there. As I was calling, a minivan carrying two older couples slowed down. &amp;quot;Do you need a place to stay?&amp;quot; one of the men asked. I told them I was considering the motel in the next town, and one of the women said &amp;quot;Oh honey! You just CAIN'T stay there! They rent those rooms by the hour!&amp;quot; The other lady added &amp;quot;That's where the truck drivers go on dates with their girlfriends!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They offered to show me where the bed and breakfast was, so I followed them a few blocks to a big old house, where I met Charlie, the elderly proprietor. After I showered, Charlie gave me leftovers from his dinner, which proved to be delicious (Charlie had lots of cookbooks in his kitchen, and apparently had studied them carefully.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterward I briefly looked over my maps, but was too tired to figure out a route, and decided to worry about it tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A First Attempt at Touring on a Single-Speed, Day Two</title>
			<link>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-two</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;I'd been tired last night, and had gone to bed without working on a route to get from Harrisburg to Cave-In-Rock, IL, on the Ohio River. From Cave-In-Rock my plan was to take the ferry and continue onto the Kentucky portion of the Trans America Trail route, the map for which I still have from my 2006 coast-to-coast trip.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<enclosure url="http://jefflee.xyz/images/southern-illinois-2.jpeg" length="0" type="image" />
			<guid>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-two</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I'd been tired last night, and had gone to bed without working on a route to get from Harrisburg to Cave-In-Rock, IL, on the Ohio River. From Cave-In-Rock my plan was to take the ferry and continue onto the Kentucky portion of the Trans America Trail route, the map for which I still have from my 2006 coast-to-coast trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How hard could it be to get to Cave-In-Rock? Pretty hard, as it turned out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I rode out of town on a short section of the Tunnel Hill Trail, then onto some quiet streets, then past the Walmart, and then onto some tree-shaded country roads. Nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-1.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few miles, though, the pavement turned to gravel. A few miles after that the gravel was bigger and rougher, and my rear tire flatted. Another pinch flat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time it took me an HOUR AND A HALF, and three patches, to get it fixed. I'd used my only spare tube on the flat yesterday, and didn't want to risk another one on the gravel, so I started walking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a while I reached pavement, turned right at the next intersection, and rode a tailwind to an impossibly busy state highway. No way was I riding 20 miles or more on that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-2.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I turned back, hoping to find a less direct, less busy, but still paved route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whitesville Road and Horseshoe Road were both great - smooth pavement and not too hilly. Shawnee Forest Road was probably the hilliest riding I'd ever done on the single-speed. Garden of Gods Road, and Karbers Ridge Road were good, but then I had to take a series of county roads that contained intermittent gravel sections which I, paranoid about getting another flat, walked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-3.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was hot now, and I was down to a few inches of water. On one of the gravel roads I spotted a woman and her young grandson in the yard of a modest home. She was happy to give me water, even inviting me into her little house and filling the bottles with ice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I alternated walking and riding the next couple of miles. During a section of rough, egg-sized gravel, I flagged down a mail man, who gave me directions and told me that I would reach pavement in half a mile or so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mail man's directions were accurate, and I was soon riding the bike instead of pushing it. I did miss one turn, climbed an unnecessary hill, fell down and bloodied my calf when I forgot to unclip, and then had a brief conversation with a local man sitting on a porch swing when I returned to the confusing intersection. &amp;quot;I tried to tell you that you were going the wrong way&amp;quot;, he said between puffs on his cigarette. I did remember him shouting something, but had assumed it was either encouragement or derision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-4.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the time I reached Cave-In-Rock it was 2:00 and I'd only done 50 miles. I was way behind schedule now, and the Utica fire department, my original destination, was clearly impossible. My revised goal was now the First Baptist Church in Sebree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After spending a few minutes in Cave-In-Rock, unsuccessfully searching for a cold soft drink, I rode the ferry across the Ohio River to Kentucky, and the state's smooth, paved roads. The rest of the afternoon passed pleasantly enough. I met a Belgium rider doing the entire TransAmerica Trail east-to-west, and talked to him for a while. Later I dropped my chain, but that was an easy repair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-5.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-6.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-7.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-two-8.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reached Sebree (population 1,561) at dusk, checked in at the church, showered, and then encountered Violet, the retired pastor's wife, who insisted that I walk across the street for a late dinner at their house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dinner I walked back to the church, set up a cot in the basement, and fell into a deep sleep, despite the presence of a railroad track behind the church.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A First Attempt at Touring on a Single-Speed, Day One</title>
			<link>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-one</link>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;The last several years I've traveled back to my home state of Kentucky to do the Redbud Ride in London, in the eastern part of the state. Organized bike rides are not really my thing, but this one is usually fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<enclosure url="http://jefflee.xyz/images/canola.jpeg" length="0" type="image" />
			<guid>http://jefflee.xyz/posts/a-first-attempt-at-touring-on-a-single-speed-day-one</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<content:encoded>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last several years I've traveled back to my home state of Kentucky to do the Redbud Ride in London, in the eastern part of the state. Organized bike rides are not really my thing, but this one is usually fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year I thought I'd &amp;quot;ride to the ride&amp;quot; from where I live in Lebanon, Illinois, about 25 miles east of St. Louis. I've wanted to try out very lightly loaded touring on my Wabi Lightning SE single-speed, and this seemed like a good opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather was nice this morning - cool, and not terribly windy at 7:00 when I rode out of my driveway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-1.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first 50+ miles were of course very familiar, since I ride the super-flat, rough chip seal Illinois farm roads around here all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-2.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last night I'd used Google Maps to work out a route that meandered south-east on lightly traveled farm roads. There would be hardly any elevation gain, so unless the wind was against me in a major way, I hoped to do a lot of miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was lucky today, and I didn't experience the often brutal south winds that are much harder than any hills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-3.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-4.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-5.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-6.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-7.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-8.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Not shown: The graffiti artist's illustration of the late John Holmes' most famous attribute.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The route had me skirting towns all morning and early afternoon, and the first place I saw that was big enough to have any services was Tamaroa (population 740.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-9.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-10.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loitered at the Casey's convenience store for a while, consuming pizza, donuts, Gatorade and Pepsi. I'd been craving ice-cold coconut water, my latest obsession, all morning, but sadly, coconut water was not available in Tamaroa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was some sort of remodeling under way at the Casey's, and the men's room had been temporarily removed. The woman behind the counter directed me to the lady's room, which was shockingly clean - far cleaner than any Casey's men's room I'd ever seen (And I've been in lots of Casey's men's rooms during long bike rides.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I was sitting on the sidewalk in front of the Casey's, eating my pizza, a young woman rode up on a spiffy yellow bike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-11.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was carrying fliers for a benefit to help her friend, Heather, and was angry that the lady who had made the fliers had omitted her friend's name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;She can't do anything right - it's like a monkey trying to fuck a football!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, I had noticed a different flier posted around town that did mention Heather's name, but it failed to include any info about what exactly was afflicting her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was mildly curious about the whole situation, but decided it was best not to ask the angry girl, and so I got back on the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-12.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was hot now, and I encountered some gravel roads, which caused me to regret my choice of 23 mm tires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, I hit a rough railroad crossing too hard and got a pinch flat. After 40 minutes I got it changed and continued on. Now I was covered with black grease from the chain, which caused me to regret my choice of white handlebar tape and white saddle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-13.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src="/posts/images/will-i-walk/day-one-14.jpeg" class="img-responsive center-block"/&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Heh.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later in the afternoon I had my usual navigational difficulties getting in and out of the larger towns of Christopher and West Frankfort. After that, though, it was ever-so-slightly-less-flat countryside until I reached Harrisburg (population 9,031), where I stopped at the first motel I saw, a shitty Super 8 without a working pop machine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I walked half a mile in the dark to Subway for dinner, then walked back to the motel and went to bed. I was tired after 128 miles, and slept soundly.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>